A Guide to the Blake W. Corson, Jr., Papers, 1861-1984 (Bulk, 1934-1979)
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series IV: Professional Projects, 1937-1984, n.d.
  - Subseries D: Research Projects
    - Sub-subseries i: Compressibility Research
      - Bernouilli's Equation for Compressible Fluids--Calculations/Graphs/Notes, 1939, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Analysis of Compressibility Loss: Propeller 3155-6--Graphs/Tables, 1941, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Compressible Flow: Propeller Efficiency-- Drawings/Graphs/Notes, 1941, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - 16-000 Series Compressibility--Calculations/Figures, 1941, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Compressibility Research: Estimation of Propeller Loss of Efficiency-- Data/Graphs/Report, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Compressibility Loss: P-60A Airplane Propeller-- Graphs/Tables, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Compressible Flow: Tube of Varying Cross Section--Calculations/Graphs/Notes, 1942-1944, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Compressible Flow: Thermal Deicing Propeller-- Calculations/Graphs/Reports, 1943, n.d.-1944 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Compressible Flow: Jet Reactions-- Calculations/Notes, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Rocket Fuel Data, 1958, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Variable Sweep--Drawing/Notes, 1960, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Sub-subseries ii: Jet Interference Program
      - Jet Interference Program: Energy Relations of Compressible Flow--Calculations/Notes, 1965, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Jet Interference Program--Notes/Proposal, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Jet Interference Program: CCO Interfacing--Photographs/Report, 1965, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Pressure Belt Analysis-- Drawings/Graphs/Photographs, 1942, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Turbo Jet Engines: Engine Comparison Tables, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Thin Wing Buffetting--Notes/Report, 1953, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Mach with Respect to HP-- Graphs/Notes, 1954-1955, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Projectiles in Eliptical Orbit Near Earth--Calculations/Drawings/Notes, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Sub-subseries iii: Boundary Layer Control
      - "Effect of Boundary Layer Control and Design Parameters on Propeller Performance at Zero Advance (BWC), n.d. (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Boundary Layer Control: Figures 1-13, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Boundary Layer Losses in Diffuser: Attempted Estimate, Ca. 1955 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - The Effect of Boundary Layer Control and Design Parameters on Propeller Performance at Zero Advance--Draft, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Constant Pressure Injector: Equations-- Graphs/Tables, 1956, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Regenerative Decomposition Unit-- Notes, 1959, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Saturn C-5 Three Stage Escape Vehicle: Stability and Drag Characteristics--Report, 1962, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Rocket Thrust-- Calculations/Notes, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Turbine Air Compression--Calculations/Graphs/Notes, 1965, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - V/STOL: Site Plan--Figures/Notes, 1966, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Oscillating Orfice Pump--Calculations/Model/Notes/Photographs, 1967, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Double Vortex Pressure Box--Data/Drawings, 1967, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous Flight Characteristics-- Calculations, Ca. 1967 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Force on a Rankine Ovid--Calculations/Notes, Ca. 1968 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Sub-subseries iv: Air Breathing Propulsions Systems
      - Air Breathing Propulsion Systems, 1968, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 37)
      - Air Breathing Propulsion Systems--Report, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Sub-subseries v: Swept Wing
      - Swept Wing Deflected: Jet Lift Propulsion Systems--Calculations/Data/Drawings/Proposal, 1968, n.d.-1969 (Box 5, Folder 39)
      - Swept Wing: Inboard Jet Flight--Calculations/Figures/Notes/ Proposal, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Sub-subseries vi: Power on Polars
      - Trimmed Power on Polars: Wind Tunnel Model--Report Draft, 1970, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 41)
      - Trimmed Power on Polars: Wind Tunnel Model-- Report, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Subseries E: 16 Foot Transonic Tunnel and Research
    - Transonic Tunnel: Test Section Air Removal-- Notes, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Transonic Tunnel Tasks: T0282, T0284, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Mass Flow Calculations, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Transonic Tunnel Energy Relation for Compression Box--Calculation/Graph, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - 16 ft Transonic High Speed Tunnel Section Information: Critical Speed--Figures, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - "The 16 ft. Transonic Wind Tunnel Calibration with Test Section Air Removal"--Report Draft, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - 16 ft. Transonic Tunnel-- Photographs, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - "The 16 ft. Transonic Wind Tunnel Calibration with Test Section Air Removal"-- Corrected Pages, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Transonic Tunnel:Transfer of Pitching Moments-- Report, 1936, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Corrections to 16 ft. Transonic Wind Tunnel Air Flow Pressure-- Figures/ Graphs, 1936, 1942, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Propeller Research-- Calculations/Drawings/Graphs/ Notes, 1936-1945, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Jet Propulsion Research-- Graphs/Notes, 1937, n.d., 1942, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Velocity Survey Ahead of Fans, 1941-1942, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Transonic Tunnel Calibrations-- Calculations/Logs/Notes, 1941-1943, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Rear Fan-- Torsional Rigidity of Blades, 1942, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Study and Alteration to the Wind Tunnel Fans--Graphs/Notes, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Rear Fan Adaptation of M.F. 7 Blade Tunnel Design, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      Messick, Mr.; Keffer, Percy; Bierman, David
    - Transonic Tunnel: 1940 Reports, 1942-1949 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Fan Blade Vibration, 1943, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 61)
      Edwards, H. B.
    - Transonic Tunnel: Front Fan Blade Vibration, 1943, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Rear Fan Blade Vibration--Graphs/Tables, 1943, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Transonic Tunnel: LMAL Propeller Dyanometer Tests--Figures, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - 16 ft. Transonic Tunnel: NACA-- Photographs, 1944, n.d.-1967 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - 16 Ft. Transonic Tunnel: Operational Data--Graphs, 1945-1947 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - S.A.E.: Propeller Shafts and Cone Dimensions-- Blueprints, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Air Removal Section--Figure/Graphs/Notes, 1946, n.d.-1965 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Two-Dimensional Profile Drag--Calculations Photographs, 1947, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Propeller Dynamometer Equiptment-- Graphs/Report, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Propeller Induced Angle of Attack-- Graphs/Notes/Tables, 1949, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Transonic Tunnel and Corson-- Photographs (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Transonic Tunnel: 1950-59 Reports, 1950-1959 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Horsepower vs. RPM Tests-- Graphs/Notes/Tables, 1951-1952, 1957, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Mass Flow (Pressure Rise through Fans)--Graphs, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Turbulence Measurements--Graphs, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Test Section--Graphs/Notes, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Loss--Notes, 1954-1955, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Transonic Tunnel:Test F-105 (Old Model)-- Drawings/Graphs/Notes, 1954-1957, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Transonic Tunnel--Notes, 1955-1956, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Wind Tunnel to be Operated with Transonic Tunnel Air Removal Compressor-- Calculations/Drawings/Notes/ Proposal, 1956, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Supersonic Addition--Calculations/Notes, 1956, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Transonic Tunnel:Calibration with Test Section Air Removal --Calculations/Graphs/Notes, 1956-1973, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Transonic Tunnel (Small) to be Powered by Compressor for B-L Removal, 1957, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Transonic Tunnel--Photographs, 1957, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Air Removal System, 1957-1960 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Transonic Tunnel: RML 52E01-- Shaft Torsion, Dampers, and Humidity (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Compressor Analysis Data, 1958-1961, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Ground Rules/ Position Request-- Notes, 1960, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Transonic Tunnel: 1960-69 Reports, 1960-1969 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Wind Tunnel Calibration With Test Section Air Removal, 1961-1973, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Size Classifications, Ca. 1962 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Balance List Completed, 1962, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Miscellaneous Facilities, Ca. 1962 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Transonic Tunnel--Figures/Graphs/Notes, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Wall Divergence--Graphs/Notes/Reports, 1963-1964, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Wind Tunnel Test Section Air Removal--Figures/Graphs, 1963-1973, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Flight, Thrust, and Drag, 1964, n.d.-1966 (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Flight and Aerodynamic Analysis, 1965-1967 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Transonic Tunnel:Subsonic WindTunnel Drag-- Calculations/Notes, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Transonic Tunnel: NASA Photographs, 1967, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Sir Frank Whittle: Visit at Langley-- Photographs, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Cooling by Direct Integration of Cool Dry Air-- Calculations/Graphs/Notes, 1967, n.d.-1979 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Transonic Tunnel:Wind Tunnel Test Section--Data/Graphs/Notes, 1969-1974, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Transonic Tunnel: 1970-1972 Reports, 1970-1972 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - "Transonic Wind Tunnel Calibration with Test Section Air Removal"--Outline (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Air Stream Turbulence, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Transonic Tunnel:Staff List, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Transonic Tunnel Calibration Report--Edits/Outline, 1973, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - " 16' Transonic Wind Tunnel Calibration with Test Section Air Removal"--Blue Card Editorial, 1973, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - "16 Foot Transonic Wind Tunnel Calibration with Test Section Air Removal"-- Tables 1-8, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - "16 Foot Transonic Wind Tunnel Calibration with Test Section Air Removal"-- Report by BWC, Runckle, and Igoe, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - "16 Foot Transonic Wind Tunnel Calibration with Test Section Air Removal"-- Figures 1-48, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - 16' Transonic Tunnel Calibration Report: Edited Copy, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - 16' Transonic Tunnel Calibration: Edited Copy with Notes--Report Draft, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - "16 Foot Transonic Wind Tunnel Calibration with Test Section Air Removal"-- Manuscript, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - "16 Foot Transonic Wind Tunnel Calibration with Test Section Air Removal"-- Unedited, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - "16 Foot Transonic Wind Tunnel Calibration with Test Section Air Removal"-- Draft by BWC, Jack F.Runckle, and William B.Igoe, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - "16 Foot Transonic Wind Tunnel Calibration with Test Section Air Removal"-- Edits with Table of Contents, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - "16 Foot Transonic Wind Tunnel Calibration with Test Section Air Removal"-- with Corrections, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - "16 Foot Transonic Wind Tunnel Calibration with Test Section Air Removal"-- Report, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - "16 Foot Transonic Wind Tunnel Calibration with Test Section Air Removal"-- Tables, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - "16 Foot Transonic Wind Tunnel Calibration with Test Section Air Removal"-- Figures/Photographs, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - "16 Foot Transonic Wind Tunnel Calibration with Test Section Air Removal"-- Copy 1, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Testing Information (Donald L. Maiden), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Wind Tunnel Design Theory--Calculations/Notes/Tables, 1976, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Transonic Tunnel: Internal Photographs, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Series V: Publications, Journals, and Reports, 1934-1982
  - Subseries A: Publications (Folder 2)
    Materials from this subseries are in Boxes 6-9 (folders listed below) and in oversize Folder 2.
    - "60,000 HP Fan Drive For the 16-Foot Tunnel," 1948 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - "8th Intersociety Energy Conservation Engineering Confrence Proceedings," 1973 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - "Aircraft Power Plant"--Patent, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - "Air Craft Propulsion Confrence"--Figure Reprints, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - "Becco 90% and 98% Hydrogen Peroxide: Properties, Records and Potential in the Propulsions Field", 1961 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - "Becco: Hydrogen Peroxide Physical Properties Book," 1955 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - "Commercial Air Transportation Developments in the Next Three Decades" by H.W. Withington, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - "High Bypass Lift/Cruise Fan: The State of the Art," 1965 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - "Concentrated Hydrogen Peroxide," 1959 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - "Concentrated Hydrogen Peroxide H202 Properties, Uses, Storage, and Handeling," 1959 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - "Encylclopedia of Chemical Technology: Manganese Compounds to Nitrophenols," Ca. 1967, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - "The Energy Dilema and its Impact on Transportation," 1973 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - "Exhaust Nozzles Lift Engines," 1964, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - "Field Handeling of Concentrated Hydrogen Peroxide," 1955, 1958, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - "Fuel Conservation Prop-Fan: Propulsion for High Speed Aircraft," 1976 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - "Investigation of the Use of Meathonal-Gasoline Blends," 1977 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - "Physical Constants and Conservation Factors Revised," 1969 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - "Performance Matching to the Propulsion System--S.A.E., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - "Selecting Construction Steels for Aircraft Design" by C.L. Hilbert, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - "A Short Method for Evaluating Determinants and Solving for Systems of Linear Equations with Real or Complex Coefficients," 1941 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - "Supersonic Systems Exhaust Nozzle Configuration Study" by W.A. Fasching and H.A. Carl, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "Supersonic Transport Mach +-2.5: Annular Exhaust System Configuration Study for Turbofan Engine" by W.A. Fasching, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - "Supersonic Transport Propulsion Considerations," 1963 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - "Theoretical Analysis of Oscillations of a Towed Cable," 1949 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "TJ70 Engine Considerations for Supersonic Transport," 1963 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "Twelfth Southeastern Seminar on Thermal Sciences", 1976 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Subseries B: Reports
    - Author Search--Research Notes, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - "16 Foot Transonic Wind Tunnel Calibration with Test Section Air Removal" -- George Strokes Editorial, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - "Aerodynamic Interface Between Exhaust System and Airframe," 1970 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - "Aerodynamic Performance of the 16-Foot Transonic Tunnel Air Removal Compressor," 1961 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - "Aerodynamic Reduction of Static-Pressure Sensing Errors for Aircraft at Subsonic, Near Sonic, and Low Super Sonic Speed," 1959 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - "The Aerodynamics of High Speed Propellers," 1976, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - "The Aerodynamics of a Wind Tunnel Fan", 1941 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - "Agricultural Alcohol in Automotive Fuel: Nebraska GASOHOL," 1973, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - "Air Flow and Power Characteristics of the Langley 16 Foot Transonic Tunnel with Slotted Test Section," 1952 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - "Analysis of Heat and Compressibility Effects in Internal Flow Systems and High-Speed Tests of a Ram Jet System ," 1943 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - "Analysis of Propeller Efficiency Losses Associated with Heated-Air Thermal Deicing ," 1945 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - "Applications of Modern Hydrodynamics to Aeronautics", 1972, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - "Calibration of the Langley 16-Foot Transonic Tunnel With Test Section Air Removal"--Personal Copy, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - "Calibration of the Langley 16-Foot Transonic Tunnel With Test Section Air Removal ," 1974 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - "Calibration of the Langley 16-Foot Transonic Tunnel with Test Section Air Removal," 1974 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - "Characteristics of the Langley 8-Foot Transonic Tunnel with Slotted Test Section," 1958 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - "Check Calibration of the ADEC 16-Ft Transonic Tunnel", 1966 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - "Closed Space Nozzles Twin Jet Configuration," 1970 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - "Comments on Russian Tu-114," 1959 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - "Compound Compressible Nozzle Flow," 1966 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - "Copper Artifacts: Correlation with Source Types Copper Ores," 1966 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - "A Correlation od High Subsonic Afterbody Drag in the Presence of a Propulsive Jet or Support Sting," 1965 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - "Effects of Compressibility on the Lift and the Load Characteristics of a Tappered Wing of NACA 64-210 Air Foil Sections," 1948 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - "Effect of Ice and Heated Air Deicing on the Aerodynamic Performance of Propellers," 1948 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - "Effect of Ice and Heated-Air Deicing on the Aerodynamic Performance of Propellers"--S.A.E., 1948 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - "The Effect of a Tip Modification and Thermal Deicing Air Flow on Propeller Performance," 1945 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - "The Elimination of Diffuser Seperation by Vortex Generators", 1947 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - "Energy Losses in Air Screw Propellers," 1938, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - "Experimentally Determined Drag of Conical Afterbodies with Effects of Jet Exiting From a Convergent Divergent Nozzle with Thin Base", 1969 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - "An Experimental Investigation of the Unsteady Flows about Spheres and Disks," 1968 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - "Facility Saftey Analysis Report: Vought Missles and Space Company," 1973 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - "Faciliy Review for Director of Langley Research Center," 1968 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - "Field of Flow About a Jet and Effect of Jets on Stability of Jet Propelled Airplanes," 1946 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - "Formulas an Charts for Designing Flexure Pivots," 1947 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - "A Glow Discharge Anemometer", 1934 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - "H2O2 Injector: p1127 Box Engine," 1959, n.d.-1960 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - "An Improved Type of Crate for Botled Beverages," 1951 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - "An Investigation of Transonic Flow Fields Surrounding Hot and Cold Sonic Jets," 1961 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - "Jet Noise Prediction," 1965 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - "The Langley 2000 Horsepower Propeller," 1952 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - "McDonnel Douglas IRAD Review," 1968, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - "Performance Characterisics of Existing Utility Boilers When Fired wih Low BTU Gas," 1974 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - "Performance of an Ethanol-Gasoline Blend in Auomobiles and Light Trucks," 1975, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - "Performance of Mutiple Jet-Exit Installations" (n-65), n.d. (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - "Performance of Variable Divergent-Nozzle Designed for Flight Mach Numbers," 1961 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - "Power Requirements of the Langley 16-Foot Transonic Tunnel with Test Section Air Removal," 1955 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - "Power Requirements of the 16-Foot Transonic Tunnel with Test Secion Air Removal" (copy), 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - "Preliminary Report to the Peninsula Planning Disrict Commission on Solid Waste Management Plan," 1976 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - "Preliminary Trial of Pressure Belt," 1942 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - "Pressure Distributions for a Sting-Mounted Cone-Cylinder Body Which Simulates the 16-Foot Transonic Tunnel Strut-Mounted Air-Powered Nacelle," 1967 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - "A Problem of Three Dimenional Hypersonic Boundary Layer Ineraction," 1968 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - "Protien Concenrates from Distillers By-Products," 1975, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - "Reduction of Noise from Unerexpanded Axisymetric Jet Flows Using Low Energy Radial Jet Flow Implement," 1965 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - "Reduction of Wall Interface for High-Lift Model Testing," 1971 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - "Second Generation Supersonic Transport," n.d. (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - "Silver Screen Catalyst Bed," 1959, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - "Stress Investigation of Axial Flow Compressor" (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - "Study and Development of Acoustic Treament for Jet Engine Tail Pipes," 1971 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - "Summary of Jet Exit Research," n.d. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - "The Transfer Function for a Laser Interferometric Angle Sensing Instrument," 1972 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - "The Transonic 16-Foot Tunnel Turbulende-Damping-Screen," n.d. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - "Variable Geometry Requirements in Inlets and Exhaust Nozzles for HIgh Mach Number Applications," 1968 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - "War Time Report: Tunnel Wall Corrections to Rolling and Yawing Moments Due to Aileron Deflection in Closed Rectangular Wind Tunnels," 1945 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Wind Tunnel Tests: Vought XF4U-1 Airplane, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Wind Tunnel Tests: Vought XF4U-1 Airplane Report Copy, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - XSB2D-1 Tests (Multiple Copies), 1942 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Subseries C: Papers
    - 8th Intersociety Energy Conservation Engineering Confrence: "Design and Demonstration of Low Emission Rankine Cycle Auto Engine Using Organic Working Fluid and Turbine Expander," 1973 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - "Combustion and Emissions Characteristics of Methanol, Methanol-Water, and Gasoline-Methanol Blends in a Spark Ignition Engine," 1976 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - "Design and Testing of a 150 Watt SNAP 19 High Performance Generator," 1973 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - "Determination of ASME Nozzle Flow Coefficients by Thrust Measurement," 1964 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - "A Dual-Element Transducer for Measuring Gas-Stream Temperatures," 1965 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - "Effects of Engine Exhaust Flow on Boattail Drag," 1970 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - "Experimental Optimization of Subsonic Inlet Design Parameters," 1966 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - "Experimental Results with Lift Engine Exhaust Nozzles," 1965 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - "Exploratory Investigation of Jet Engine Silencing with Plug Nozzle Configurations" (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - "Flow and Acoustic Charecteristics of 191 Tubes and 191 Shrouds Supersonic Jet Noise Supressor," 1971 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - "H2O2 Auxiliary Power Unit for Space Shuttle Vehicles," 1973 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - "The Jet Flap Diffuser: A New Thrust Augumenting Device," 1969 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - "Large Scale Terrestrial Solar Cell Power Generation Cost: A Preliminary Assessment," 1971 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - "Prespectives of SST Aircraft Noise Problem," 1958 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - "Methanol Technology and Economics ," Ca. 1970, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - "Methanol: A Versatile Fuel for Immediate Use," Ca. 1973, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - "Mixed Flow Nozzle Turbofan Propulsion Simulation with an Air Driven Model Engine," 1971, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - "Multielement Suppressor Nozzles for Thrust Augmentation Systems," 1972 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - "Nebraska Statutes: The Basis for the Gasohol Program," 1976, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - "The Nebraska GASOHOL Program, Providing Food and Fuel for the Future," 1976 (Box 8, Folder 30)